[
  {
    "answer": "9",
    "question": "1 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "18",
    "question": "2 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "27",
    "question": "3 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "36",
    "question": "4 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "45",
    "question": "5 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "54",
    "question": "6 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "63",
    "question": "7 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "72",
    "question": "8 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "81",
    "question": "9 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "90",
    "question": "10 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "99",
    "question": "11 x 9"
  },
  {
    "answer": "108",
    "question": "12 x 9"
  }
]
